vacationrentalpeople.com 2008-12-18

# Vacationrentalpeople.com Privacy Policy

**Vacation Rental People.com LTD  ** **PRIVACY POLICY**

**Who we are**

In this privacy policy, references to "we", "us", "our" and "Vacation Rental People" refer to Vacation Rental People.Com LTD . References to "our Website" or "the Website" refer jointly to the publically available [www.vacationrentalpeople.com](http://www.vacationrentalpeople.com/) site and to the system used by registered owners at [http://owners.vacationrentalpeople.com](http://owners.vacationrentalpeople.com/)

**What information we collect and how**

The information we collect via the Website may include.

  1. Any personal details you knowingly provide us with through forms and our email, such as name, address, telephone number etc.

  2. Your preferences and use of email updates, recorded by emails we send you (if you select to receive email updates on products and offers).
  3. Your IP Address, this is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the Website. This information is used to monitor your usage of the Website.

  4. Data recorded by the Website which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings, this saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the site. Such data is recorded locally on you computer through the use of cookies. Most browsers can be programmed to reject, or warn you before downloading cookies, information regarding this may be found in your browsers "help" facility.

**What we do with your information**

Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. The details we collect :

  1. Except as detailed below, the personal information that you give us will never be supplied to anyone outside Vacation Rental People without first obtaining your consent, unless we are obliged or permitted by law to disclose it.

  2. May be used to process any order you may make, to provide after sales service (we may pass your details to another organisation to supply/deliver products or services you have purchased and/or to provide after-sales service);

  3. We may not use your email address to send you information on our other products and services unless you have expressly consented, or is permitted by our general Terms & Conditions. 

  4. In order to effectively process credit or debit card transactions it may be necessary for the bank or card processing agency to verify your personal details for authorisation outside the European Economic Area (EEA).

  5. We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes unless you have expressly consented to this.

  6. We may store your personal data on systems located outside the EEA , ensuring appropriate safeguards are in place to restrict unauthorised access.

**Your Rights**

You have the right to request a copy of any information that we currently hold about you. In order to receive such information please send your contact details including address and payment of 10 UK Pounds to cover administration expenses to the following address:

Privacy

Vacation Rental People.com LTD

89a The Broadway

Wimbledon

SW19 1QE

**Other Websites**

This privacy policy only covers the websites listed above. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.

Privacy V1.1 February 2008

Modification History :  
1.0 to 1.1 : Modified point 3 of "What we do with your information" to permit usage as per our T&C's
